shemalemodelstube.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy of shemalemodelstube.com

## Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  *     * ### Analytics

      * ### Clicky

Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data

    * ### Contacting the User

      * ### Contact form

Personal Data: email address; first name; various types of Data

    * ### Content commenting

      * ### Comment system managed directly

Personal Data: Cookies; first name

    * ### Displaying content from external platforms

      * ### Google Fonts

Personal Data: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

      * ### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets

Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data

    * ### Social features

      * ### Public profile

Personal Data: country; first name; gender; last name

## Further information about Personal Data

  *     * ### Links

The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Site they should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. 

    * ### Legal Age Usage

Our Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18 or 21 depending on the age of majority in your jurisdiction. This site is strictly for adults as it is an adult entertainment website. Our Site does not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit. We also encourage third party programs to help keep adult material from prying children’s eyes. 

    * ### Affiliate Links

This Website has a number of affiliate banner links that go to external adult sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of those sites. Affiliate links are from sponsors such as Grooby, Smc Revenue, Island Dollars, Fame Dollars and many more. Please exercise caution on any site and understand the privacy rules of each and what user data they may or may not be requesting form you. 

    * ### Hosting

The website is hosted on Techie Media Database located in New Jersey, United States. For more information on the hosting services please visit techiemedia.com 

    * ### SPAM Protection

This site has a custom CAPTCHA when using the comment and contact forms. The comments also must be approved by the administrator before they are published publicly. We delete comments that include personal information such as but not limited to information such as phone numbers, home address, email address and links to other sites. 

    * ### The Service is not directed to children under the age of 13

Users declare themselves to be adult according to their applicable legislation. Minors may use this Website only with the assistance of a parent or guardian. Under no circumstance persons under the age of 13 may use this Website.

  *     * ### Owner and Data Controller

SMT Administrator

**Owner contact email:** info@ladyboyportal.com
